<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Jobs>
	<Job>
		<Title>Accounting and Budget</Title>	
		<Description>Develop new financial policies, principles, and procedures.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Computer Engineer</Title>	
		<Description>Develop test plans to test computer software functions and computer devices.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Electrical Engineer</Title>	
		<Description>Manage special projects and keep the grid running smoothly.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>General Engineer</Title>	
		<Description>Help develop oxy-combustion, solid oxide fuel cells, and chemical looping technologies.</Description>
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Nuclear Engineer</Title>	
		<Description>Help assess the operations and procedures of nuclear processing facilities.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Information Technology</Title>	
		<Description>Support, implement, and program software systems and applications.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Operations Research Analyst</Title>	
		<Description>Design and conduct tests that reflect real-world issues, problems, and environments.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Industry Economist</Title>	
		<Description>Explore and analyze the trends and issues facing the world's energy economies and markets.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Physicist</Title>	
		<Description>Be a part of research programs and projects in the area of instrumentation in Nuclear Physics.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>High Voltage Electrician</Title>	
		<Description>Interface with high voltage equipment and install transformers, circuit breakers, and capacitors.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Electronics Engineer/Title>	
		<Description>Provide electronic engineering associated with communications systems and ensure the systems operate correctly.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Economist</Title>	
		<Description>Conduct economic analyses and prepare forecasts for different energy markets.  Be on top of the latest trends in the world's energy economies.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Public Utilities Specialist</Title>	
		<Description>Complete energy settlement transactions and manage a variety of projects. Develop contracts to sell power to wholesale customers.</Description>	
	</Job>
	<Job>
		<Title>Statistical Mathematician</Title>	
		<Description>Use statistical computing software to research, analyze, and process energy pricing, production, supply, and distribution data.</Description>	
	</Job>
</Jobs>